Guide to the Amil Gargano papers, 1960-2011 and undated RL.11364
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1970-2011 and undated; 7
  - Original Materials, 1970-2011 and undated; 1
    - Ally and Gargano--Ciba Geigy Historical #3: 14 spots, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-024)
    - Ally and Gargano--Clio Award Winners, 1986 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-025)
    - Ally and Gargano--Commodore: 7 spots, Undated (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-026)
    - Ally and Gargano--Commodore Cassette 1: 20 spots, 1982 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-027)
    - Ally and Gargano--Commodore: 20 spots, 1982 (Box AV2, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-028)
    - Ally and Gargano--Commodore: 20 spots, 1982 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-029)
    - Ally and Gargano--Comp-U-Card Cassette 1: Historical, 1984 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-030)
    - Ally and Gargano--Comparative Advertising: 39 spots, 1995 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-031)
    - Ally and Gargano--Current Clients/Classics/ Partnership for a Drug Free America, 1990 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-032)
    - Ally and Gargano--Fashion: Barney's, Calvin Klein, 1991 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-033)
    - Ally and Gargano--Federal Express "Fast Paced World", 1990 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-034)
    - Ally and Gargano--Federal Express Smithsonian Institution presentation, 1988 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-035)
    - Ally and Gargano--Fiat: Flip/Waterfall, 1990 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-036)
    - Ally and Gargano--Fiat Cassette 3: Historical 13 spots, Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-037)
    - Ally and Gargano--Fiat Cassette 4: 7 spots, Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-038)
    - Ally and Gargano--Fiat "Waterfall", 1990 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-039)
    - Ally and Gargano--Fiat, Tonka, Timberland spots, Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-040)
    - Ally and Gargano--Hertz reel: 10 spots, Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-041)
    - Ally and Gargano--Historical agency reel: 56 spots, 1990 (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-042)
    - Ally and Gargano--IBM Cassette 1: Historical 64 spots, Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-043)
    - Ally and Gargano--Karastan Cassette 1: Historical 5 spots, Undated (Box AV3, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-044)
    - Ally and Gargano--Long Distance Carriers: Adbank video compilation, 1992 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-045)
    - Ally and Gargano--Market Segmentation: MCI, Barney's, Dunkin Donuts, Commodore, 1986 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-046)
    - Ally and Gargano--MCI Cassette 1: 9 spots, 1986 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-047)
    - Ally and Gargano--National Distillers/Keller Geister Wine Cassette 1: 4 spots, 1985 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-048)
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business 14:00, 1981 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-049)
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business 14:00, 1981 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-050)
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business 14:00, 1981 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-051)
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business 14:00, 1981 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11364-VHS-002)
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business 14:00, 1981 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11364-VHS-003)
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business: Leg Room/Fiat 124, 1990 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-052)
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business Presentation 20:00, 1981 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-053)
    - Ally and Gargano--New Product Introductions: 31 segments, 1991 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-054)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pan Am: 8 spots, 1990 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-055)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pan Am: 11 spots, 1986 (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-056)
    - Ally and Gargano--Partnership for a Drug Free America: 7 spots, Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-057)
    - Ally and Gargano--Partnership for a Drug Free America Round 1, Undated (Box AV4, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-058)
    - Ally and Gargano--Partnership for a Drug Free America Round 2, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-059)
    - Ally and Gargano--Partnership for a Drug-Free America 36 spots, Undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11364-VHS-004)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pentax "Fear", 1990 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-060)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pfizer Cassette 1: Historical 12 spots, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-061)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pfizer Plax "Audience", 1991 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-062)
    - Ally and Gargano--Polaroid Casssette 6: 11 spots, 1986 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-063)
    - Ally and Gargano--Polaroid Casssette 7: 4 spots, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-064)
    - Ally and Gargano--Polaroid Casssette 10: Historical 39 spots, 1986 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-065)
    - Ally and Gargano--Polaroid part 2 and current clients, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-066)
    - Ally and Gargano--Presentation reel: 23 spots, 1986 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-067)
    - Ally and Gargano--Reebok :60, 1990 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-068)
    - Ally and Gargano--Saab Cassette 5: Saab 9000 5 spots, 1986 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-069)
    - Ally and Gargano--Saab Cassette 6: Historical 6 spots, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-070)
    - Ally and Gargano--Scrambled :30, Undated (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-071)
    - Ally and Gargano--Screening reel (Barney's Cassette 1): 7 spots, 1980 (Box AV5, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-072)
    - Ally and Gargano--Shearson reel, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-073)
    - Ally and Gargano--Shearson Lehman Brothers: 4 spots on air, 1990 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-074)
    - Ally and Gargano--Shofar presentation reel: 17 spots, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-075)
    - Ally and Gargano--Showtime Historical #1, 1991 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-076)
    - Ally and Gargano--Showtime Networks "Stadium", 1990 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-077)
    - Ally and Gargano--Showtime Networks "Side by Side" summer spots, 1990 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-078)
    - Ally and Gargano--Take-5 Shearson: 2 spots, 1989 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-079)
    - Ally and Gargano--Time Magazine Cassette 3, 1983 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-080)
    - Ally and Gargano--Time Magazine Cassette 4, 1983 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-081)
    - Ally and Gargano--Time Magazine Cassette 2, 1983 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-082)
    - Ally and Gargano--Tonka Cassette 1: Historical 8 sots, 1986 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-083)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travel reel: Hertz, Pan Am, 1983 (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-084)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travel reel: Hertz, Pan Am, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-085)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travel reel: Hertz, Pan Am, Undated (Box AV6, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-086)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travelers Insurance: Squeezing/Interview, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-087)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travelers Insurance Cassette 1: 6 spots, 1976 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-088)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travelers Insurance Cassette 2: Father of Two Kids/Tornado, 1976 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-089)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travelers Insurance Cassette 3: Man and Machine/Agents, 1974 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-090)
    - Ally and Gargano--Twenty Year Span of Television: 25 spots, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-091)
    - Ally and Gargano--Twenty Seven spot reel, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-092)
    - Ally and Gargano--University of Syracuse Presentation Reel, 1987 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-093)
    - Ally and Gargano--Various products: 22 spots, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-094)
    - Ally and Gargano--Volvo/Fiat/Saab, 1989 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-095)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Agency reel, Undated (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-096)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Alabama Power: 10 spots, 1997 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-097)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Alabama Power: Cost of Living cable version, 1994 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-098)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Alabama Power: Instuctions, 1995 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-099)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Alabama Power: Marketing "Same Everything", 1995 (Box AV7, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-100)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Alabama Power: Tragic Waste/An Alternative, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-101)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Alabama Power: Tragic Waste/An Alternative, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-102)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Alabama Power spots, 1997 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11364-BCAM-001)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Audiovox spots, 1994 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-103)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Audiovox: Minivox Lite "More Features", 1993 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-104)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Ballpark Franks/Mr. Turkey spots, 1993 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-105)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Case Studies: Dunkin Donuts, Showtime, BONY, Shearson, 1992 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-106)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Compilation reel, 2010 (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11364-DBCAM-001)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Current Work, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-107)
      Alabama Power, Shearson, LCI, Audiovox, Showtime, NYNEX
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Current work showreel, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-108)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Fashion reel: Barney's, Calvin Klein, Timberland, Undated (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-109)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Historical reel, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-110)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--LCI International presentation reel, 1992 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-111)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--New Business reel, 1994 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-112)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--New Business reel, 1995 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-113)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--New Business reel, 1996 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-114)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--New Business reel, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-115)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--New Business reel, 1991 (Box AV8, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-116)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--NYNEX presentation reel, 1993 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-117)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Pete Peterson "Facing Up", 1993 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-118)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Showreel with the first half of "over the years", Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-119)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Ally and Gargaon showreel, Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-120)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Showreel with titles, Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-121)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Showtime agency version, 1994 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-122)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Showtime "Multiple Televisions", 1991 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-123)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Showtime "Side by Side", Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-124)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Showtime "You Decide", Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-125)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Timberland "Getting Soaked", Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-126)
    - General and Personal--Carl Ally Historical Reel 60:00, 1975 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-127)
    - General and Personal--Carl Ally Package Goods Reel 18:00, 1976 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-128)
    - General and Personal--Last Dark Days: Sight Savers International film written and directed by Amil Gargano, Undated (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-129)
    - General and Personal--They Shoot Films; LCI, 1992 (Box AV9, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-130)
    - General and Personal--Untitled, Undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-131)
    - General and Personal--Untitled, Undated (Box AV10, Video-cassette RL11364-UMATIC-132)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency historical 14, 1982 (Box AV11, Film-reel RL11364-F16-001)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel, Undated (Box AV11, Film-reel RL11364-F16-002)
      Federal Express, MCI, Dunkin' Donuts, Travelers, Fiat, Tonka, Hertz, Timberland, Calvin Klein, Pentax, IBM, Saab, Commodore, Barney's, Keller Geister, Pan Am
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel, Undated (Box AV11, Film-reel RL11364-F16-003)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel historical 32 spots, Undated (Box AV11, Film-reel RL11364-F16-004)
    - Ally and Gargano--Case studies: MCI, Federal Express, Dunkin Donuts, Undated (Box AV11, Film-reel RL11364-F16-005)
    - Ally and Gargano--Celebrity Presenters Reel, 1985 (Box AV11, Film-reel RL11364-F16-006)
      Travelers (Gregory Peck); Pan Am (Bill Cosby, Joan Crawford, David Niven)
    - Ally and Gargano--Competitive reel, 1979 (Box AV11, Film-reel RL11364-F16-007)
      Volvo, Krystal, Hertz, Fiat, Pan Am, Federal Express, IBM, Tonka, Travelers, Corning, Dunkin Donut
    - Ally and Gargano--Current television reel, 1982 (Box AV11, Film-reel RL11364-F16-008)
      Timberland, Pentax, Time, Kayser-Roth, BONY, Saab, Comprehensive Accounting, Pentax, Travelers, Saab
    - Ally and Gargano--Federal Express, Undated (Box AV12, Film-reel RL11364-F16-009)
    - Ally and Gargano--Federal Express client reel 1, Undated (Box AV12, Film-reel RL11364-F16-010)
    - Ally and Gargano--Fiat client reel, 1978 (Box AV12, Film-reel RL11364-F16-011)
    - Ally and Gargano--General reel 49 spots, Undated (Box AV12, Film-reel RL11364-F16-012)
    - Ally and Gargano--General reel/Tesch 34 spots, 1978 (Box AV12, Film-reel RL11364-F16-013)
    - Ally and Gargano--Hertz and Pan Am/Club Med speech, Undated (Box AV12, Film-reel RL11364-F16-014)
    - Ally and Gargano--Hertz client reel B, Undated (Box AV12, Film-reel RL11364-F16-015)
    - Ally and Gargano--Historical reel, 1979 (Box AV12, Film-reel RL11364-F16-016)
      Federal Express, Barney's, Dunkin Donut, Harry and David, Pentax, Travelers
    - Ally and Gargano--Historical reel, 1975-1976 (Box AV13, Film-reel RL11364-F16-017)
      IBM, Federal Express, Travelers, Pan Am, Pharmacraaft, Fiat, Tonka
    - Ally and Gargano--Historical reel, 1977-1978 (Box AV13, Film-reel RL11364-F16-018)
      Tonka, Fiat, Federal Express, Pan Am, Travelers, Dunkin Donut, Barney's,
    - Ally and Gargano--Historical reel, 1981 (Box AV13, Film-reel RL11364-F16-019)
      Bay Bank, Travelers, Karastan, MCI, Saab, Federal Express, Pentax, Dunkin Donut, Timberland, Time
    - Ally and Gargano--Historical reel, 1980 (Box AV13, Film-reel RL11364-F16-020)
      Barney's, Huffman-Koos, Male Jeans, MCI, Saab, Pentax, Travelers, Federal Express, Bay Banks, Kayser-Roth
    - Ally and Gargano--Historical reel, 1984 (Box AV13, Film-reel RL11364-F16-021)
    - Ally and Gargano--IBM client reel 34 spots, Undated (Box AV13, Film-reel RL11364-F16-022)
    - Ally and Gargano--Northeast Airlines 30 spots, Undated (Box AV13, Film-reel RL11364-F16-023)
    - Ally and Gargano--Old New Business, Undated (Box AV13, Film-reel RL11364-F16-024)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pan Am client reel 2: 42 spots, Undated (Box AV14, Film-reel RL11364-F16-025)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pan Am history no. 1, Undated (Box AV14, Film-reel RL11364-F16-026)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travelers 23 spots, 1982 (Box AV14, Film-reel RL11364-F16-027)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travelers case history 1, Undated (Box AV14, Film-reel RL11364-F16-028)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travelers client reel 2 18 spots, Undated (Box AV14, Film-reel RL11364-F16-029)
    - Ally and Gargano--Tyco, 1982 (Box AV14, Film-reel RL11364-F16-030)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Amil Gargano reel 1, Undated (Box AV14, Film-reel RL11364-F16-031)
    - Amil Gargano and Partners--Amil Gargano reel 3, 1986 (Box AV14, Film-reel RL11364-F16-032)
      Federal Express, Sanyo, Polaroid, Saab, Pfizer, Calvin Klein, National Distillers, Bristol Myers, MCI, Timberland, Pan Am, Dunkin Donuts, Acutrim, Bryan Foods
    - Ally and Gargano--Bank of New York client reel, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-033)
    - Ally and Gargano--Bay Banks, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-034)
    - Ally and Gargano--Bristol Myers, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-035)
    - Ally and Gargano--Calvin Klein, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-036)
    - Ally and Gargano--Ciba-Geigy, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-037)
    - Ally and Gargano--Comprehensive Accounting client reel, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-038)
    - Ally and Gargano--Dunkin' Donuts, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-039)
    - Ally and Gargano--Hertz case history, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-040)
    - Ally and Gargano--Huffman Koos, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-041)
    - Ally and Gargano--Jergens client reel, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-042)
    - Ally and Gargano--Kalback, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-043)
    - Ally and Gargano--Karastan, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-044)
    - Ally and Gargano--Kloss Novabeam, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-045)
    - Ally and Gargano--Midway client reel, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-046)
    - Ally and Gargano--Five Minute show reel, 1986 (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-047)
    - Ally and Gargano--Karastan new business presentation, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-048)
    - Ally and Gargano--MCI Burt Lancaster/Joan Rivers case history, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-049)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pentax client reel 24 spots, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-050)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pentax case history, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-051)
    - Ally and Gargano--Personality Spokesman, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-052)
      Travelers (Gregory Peck, Len Cariow); Pan Am (Bill Cosby, David Niven)
    - Ally and Gargano--Travelers case history, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-053)
    - Ally and Gargano--Atlas Supply Company new business, 1978 (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-054)
      Fiat, IBM, Federal Express, Tonka, Pan Am, Travelers, Corning, Hertz, Dunkin Donuts
    - Ally and Gargano--Cansica client reel, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-055)
    - Ally and Gargano--Dunkin' Donuts 11 spots, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-056)
    - Ally and Gargano--Federal Express 12 spots, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-057)
    - Ally and Gargano--Federal Express Gemni, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-058)
    - Ally and Gargano--Fiat international spots, Undated (Box AV15, Film-reel RL11364-F16-059)
    - Ally and Gargano--Advertising Age reel, Undated (Box AV16, Film-reel RL11364-F16-060)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel, 1986 (Box AV16, Film-reel RL11364-F16-061)
      American Cancer Society, Bank of New York, Federal Express, MCI, Oral Research, Pfizer, Saab, Glacial Confections
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel, 1985 (Box AV16, Film-reel RL11364-F16-062)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel for Tyco, 1979 (Box AV16, Film-reel RL11364-F16-063)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel new business presentations, Undated (Box AV16, Film-reel RL11364-F16-064)
    - Ally and Gargano--Agency reel, Undated (Box AV16, Film-reel RL11364-F16-065)
    - Ally and Gargano--Automotive reel: Volvo, Fiat, Undated (Box AV16, Film-reel RL11364-F16-066)
    - Ally and Gargano--Automotive reel: Volvo, Fiat, Saab, Undated (Box AV16, Film-reel RL11364-F16-067)
    - Ally and Gargano--Bay Banks presentation reel, Undated (Box AV16, Film-reel RL11364-F16-068)
    - Ally and Gargano--Christmas party reel, 1986 (Box AV17, Film-reel RL11364-F16-069)
    - Ally and Gargano--Ciba-Geigy, Undated (Box AV17, Film-reel RL11364-F16-070)
    - Ally and Gargano--Compilation reel, Undated (Box AV17, Film-reel RL11364-F16-071)
      Pharmacraft, Hertz, Pan Am, Fiat, Barney's, Calvin Klein
    - Ally and Gargano--Compilation reel, 1981 (Box AV17, Film-reel RL11364-F16-072)
      MCI, Pan Am, Barney's, Travelers, Pentax, Federal Express, Kayser Roth, Rise, Dunkin Donuts, Keller Geister, CAC
    - Ally and Gargano--Condensed new business reel, Undated (Box AV17, Film-reel RL11364-F16-073)
    - Ally and Gargano--D. Vishach reel, Undated (Box AV17, Film-reel RL11364-F16-074)
    - Ally and Gargano--Dunkin Donuts presentation reel, Undated (Box AV17, Film-reel RL11364-F16-075)
    - Ally and Gargano--Federal Express client reel 2, Undated (Box AV17, Film-reel RL11364-F16-076)
    - Ally and Gargano--Fiat reel, Undated (Box AV17, Film-reel RL11364-F16-077)
    - Ally and Gargano--General reel, Undated (Box AV18, Film-reel RL11364-F16-078)
      Fiat, Pan Am, Barney's, Tonka, Pentax, MCI
    - Ally and Gargano--Hershey packaged goods presentation, Undated (Box AV18, Film-reel RL11364-F16-079)
    - Ally and Gargano--IBM reel, Undated (Box AV18, Film-reel RL11364-F16-080)
    - Ally and Gargano--Jergens sales meeting general reel, Undated (Box AV18, Film-reel RL11364-F16-081)
      Federal Express, MCI, Dunkin' Donuts, Saab, Bristol Myers, Ciba-Geigy, Polaroid, Jergens
    - Ally and Gargano--Kirin Beer new business, Undated (Box AV18, Film-reel RL11364-F16-082)
    - Ally and Gargano--Miscellaneous reel 1, Undated (Box AV18, Film-reel RL11364-F16-083)
      Pan Am, Barney's, Pentax, Travelers, MCI
    - Ally and Gargano--New business presentation to Tyco, 1979 (Box AV18, Film-reel RL11364-F16-084)
    - Ally and Gargano--New business presentation reel, 1980 (Box AV18, Film-reel RL11364-F16-085)
      Federal Express, Dunkin Donuts, IBM, Pentax, Tonka, Male Jeans, MCI, Huffman Koos, Barney's, Corning, Fiat
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business, 1982 (Box AV18, Film-reel RL11364-F16-086)
      Federal Express, Dunkin Donuts, MCI
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business six month reel, 1985 (Box AV19, Film-reel RL11364-F16-087)
      Ciba-Geigy, Bristol Myers, Saab, Andrew Jergens, Dunkin Donuts, Polaroid, Sun Banks, MCI, Bank of New York
    - Ally and Gargano--New Business reel for Publishers Clearing House, Undated (Box AV19, Film-reel RL11364-F16-088)
    - Ally and Gargano--Oral Research/Plax pitch, 1986 (Box AV19, Film-reel RL11364-F16-089)
    - Ally and Gargano--Packaged Goods presentation reel, 1979 (Box AV19, Film-reel RL11364-F16-090)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pentax presentation, 1986 (Box AV19, Film-reel RL11364-F16-091)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pentax animatic reel, Undated (Box AV19, Film-reel RL11364-F16-092)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pentax sales meeting, 1980 (Box AV19, Film-reel RL11364-F16-093)
    - Ally and Gargano--Pentax sales meeting, 1979 (Box AV19, Film-reel RL11364-F16-094)
    - Ally and Gargano--Publishers Clearing House presentation reel, 1980 (Box AV19, Film-reel RL11364-F16-095)
      Barney's, MCI, Pentax, Fiat, Travelers, Pan Am, MCI, Dunkin Donuts,
    - Ally and Gargano--Six Month Reel, 1979 (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-096)
      Federal Express, Pentax, Barney's, Dunkin Donuts, Travelers, Huffman Koos, Male Jeans
    - Ally and Gargano--Six Month Screening Reel, 1979 (Box AV20, Film-reel RL11364-F16-097)